{
    "id": "3260dc7f9c694b2eb88d4c2b93faf854",
    "title": "Sequence of tenses: grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "d73c2dcd85004f80811d9e76d6a3aca7",
            "title": "Sequence of Tenses Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Suddenly she gave a loud scream and ……………………… to the ground.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "fell",
                        "has fallen",
                        "had fallen"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "After questioning he ………………… to go home.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "allowed",
                        "had allowed",
                        "was allowed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "They would have won if they …………………. a bit harder.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "played",
                        "have played",
                        "had played"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ………………….. to say that she disagreed.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "heard",
                        "was heard",
                        "had heard"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Although they …………………… defeated, they did not lose heart.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "are",
                        "were",
                        "has been"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Our teacher taught us that virtue …………………… . its own reward.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "was",
                        "has been"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The teacher asked the boys whether they …………………… . the problems.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "solved",
                        "have solved",
                        "had solved"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He declared that he would not believe it even if he ……………………… it with his own eyes.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "saw",
                        "have seen",
                        "had seen"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The room ……………………… but the police failed to find anything suspicious.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "searched",
                        "was searched",
                        "had searched"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The government has announced that taxes …………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will raise",
                        "will be raised",
                        "would be raised"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}